<CATALOG>

    <MOVIE>
        <TITLE>Brightburn</TITLE>
        <REGIZOR>David Yarovesky</REGIZOR>
        <COUNTRY>USA</COUNTRY>
        <COMPANY>Columbia</COMPANY>
        <PRICE>10.90</PRICE>
        <YEAR>9 mai 2019</YEAR>
        <URLPOSTER>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/f/fa/Brightburn_film_poster.png</URLPOSTER>
        <ABOUT>Brightburn is a 2019 American superhero horror film directed by David Yarovesky, written by Mark Gunn and Brian Gunn, and produced by James Gunn and Kenneth Huang. It stars Elizabeth Banks, David Denman, Jackson A. Dunn, Matt Jones and Meredith Hagner. It follows Brandon Breyer, a young boy of extraterrestrial origin reared on Earth who realizes he has superpowers. Upon learning of them and being brainwashed by the ship he arrived in, Brandon rejects his humanity and turns to evil, opting to terrorize his hometown, including his parents. The film was produced and financed by Screen Gems, Stage 6 Films, The H Collective and Troll Court Entertainment.Brightburn was announced as Untitled James Gunn Horror Project in December 2017. Aside from Gunn producing the film, his cousin Mark and brother Brian Gunn wrote the screenplay. Principal photography began in March 2018 and wrapped in May of that same year. It adapts the concept of Superman for explicit horror.Brightburn was released in the United States on May 24, 2019 by Sony Pictures Releasing. It received mixed reviews from critics, who felt that the film did not deliver on the full potential of its premise. The film earned $32 million against a budget of $6–12 million.
        </ABOUT>
        <URLVIDEO></URLVIDEO>
    </MOVIE>
    <MOVIE>
        <TITLE>In the Heights</TITLE>
        <REGIZOR>Jon Chu</REGIZOR>
        <COUNTRY>USA</COUNTRY>
        <COMPANY>Columbia</COMPANY>
        <PRICE>10.90</PRICE>
        <YEAR>9 mai 2019</YEAR>
        <URLPOSTER>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/6/6a/In_The_Heights_teaser_poster.jpg</URLPOSTER>
        <ABOUT>In the Heights is a 2021 American musical drama film based on the stage musical of the same name by Quiara Alegría Hudes and Lin-Manuel Miranda. Directed by Jon M. Chu from a screenplay by Hudes, the film stars Anthony Ramos, Corey Hawkins, Leslie Grace, Melissa Barrera, Olga Merediz, Daphne Rubin-Vega, Gregory Diaz IV, and Jimmy Smits. The film follows a similar plot to the musical, telling the story of a corner in the Washington Heights neighborhood of Upper Manhattan in New York City, where each member of the community pursues their dream of a better life.

In the Heights was originally set to be adapted by Universal Pictures in 2008, with Kenny Ortega hired to direct. After that version fell through, the project was eventually started back up in 2016, with Chu set to direct and Ramos being cast in October 2018. The rest of the cast joined in April 2019, and filming took place around New York City that summer.

Originally intended to be released in 2020, In the Heights was postponed due to the COVID-19 pandemic. The film had its world premiere at the Los Angeles Latino International Film Festival on June 4, 2021, and was released in the United States on June 10 in theaters and simultaneously streaming on HBO Max for a month. It received acclaim from critics, with praise for Chu's direction, the story, and musical numbers.
        </ABOUT>
        <URLVIDEO></URLVIDEO>
    </MOVIE>
    <MOVIE>
        <TITLE>The Conjuring: The Devil Made Me Do It</TITLE>
        <REGIZOR>David Yarovesky</REGIZOR>
        <COUNTRY>USA</COUNTRY>
        <COMPANY>Columbia</COMPANY>
        <PRICE>10.90</PRICE>
        <YEAR>9 mai 2019</YEAR>
        <URLPOSTER>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/e/e8/The_Conjuring_-_The_Devil_Made_Me_Do_It.png</URLPOSTER>
        <ABOUT>The Conjuring: The Devil Made Me Do It (also known as The Conjuring 3) is a 2021 American supernatural horror film directed by Michael Chaves, with a screenplay by David Leslie Johnson-McGoldrick from a story by Johnson-McGoldrick and James Wan. The film serves as a sequel to The Conjuring (2013) and The Conjuring 2 (2016), and as the eighth installment in the Conjuring Universe. Patrick Wilson and Vera Farmiga reprise their roles as paranormal investigators and authors Ed and Lorraine Warren, with Ruairi O'Connor, Sarah Catherine Hook, and Julian Hilliard also starring. Wan and Peter Safran return to produce the film, which is based on the trial of Arne Cheyenne Johnson, a murder trial that took place in 1981 Connecticut, in addition to The Devil in Connecticut, a book about the trial written by Gerald Brittle.

Initial development for a third Conjuring film began in 2016, though Wan stated that he would not be directing another film in the series due to scheduling conflicts with other projects. Safran confirmed that the next film would not be a haunted house film. By June 2017, it was officially announced that a third installment was in development, with David Leslie Johnson hired to write the screenplay. Michael Chaves was announced as the film's director, after previously directing The Curse of La Llorona (2019). Filming took place in Georgia in summer 2019.

Originally slated for a September 2020 release, the film was delayed due to the COVID-19 pandemic. The Conjuring: The Devil Made Me Do It was released by Warner Bros. Pictures and New Line Cinema in the United States on June 4, 2021, where it also has a simultaneous month-long release on the HBO Max streaming service. The film has grossed $112 million against a budget of $39 million and received mixed reviews from critics, who praised the performances of Wilson and Farmiga, but noted it as weaker than previous Conjuring installments.</ABOUT>
        <URLVIDEO></URLVIDEO>
    </MOVIE>
    <MOVIE>
        <TITLE>Brightburn</TITLE>
        <REGIZOR>David Yarovesky</REGIZOR>
        <COUNTRY>USA</COUNTRY>
        <COMPANY>Columbia</COMPANY>
        <PRICE>10.90</PRICE>
        <YEAR>9 mai 2019</YEAR>
        <URLPOSTER>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/f/fa/Brightburn_film_poster.png</URLPOSTER>
        <ABOUT>Brightburn is a 2019 American superhero horror film directed by David Yarovesky, written by Mark Gunn and Brian Gunn, and produced by James Gunn and Kenneth Huang. It stars Elizabeth Banks, David Denman, Jackson A. Dunn, Matt Jones and Meredith Hagner. It follows Brandon Breyer, a young boy of extraterrestrial origin reared on Earth who realizes he has superpowers. Upon learning of them and being brainwashed by the ship he arrived in, Brandon rejects his humanity and turns to evil, opting to terrorize his hometown, including his parents. The film was produced and financed by Screen Gems, Stage 6 Films, The H Collective and Troll Court Entertainment.Brightburn was announced as Untitled James Gunn Horror Project in December 2017. Aside from Gunn producing the film, his cousin Mark and brother Brian Gunn wrote the screenplay. Principal photography began in March 2018 and wrapped in May of that same year. It adapts the concept of Superman for explicit horror.Brightburn was released in the United States on May 24, 2019 by Sony Pictures Releasing. It received mixed reviews from critics, who felt that the film did not deliver on the full potential of its premise. The film earned $32 million against a budget of $6–12 million.
        </ABOUT>
        <URLVIDEO></URLVIDEO>
    </MOVIE>
    <MOVIE>
        <TITLE>Brightburn</TITLE>
        <REGIZOR>David Yarovesky</REGIZOR>
        <COUNTRY>USA</COUNTRY>
        <COMPANY>Columbia</COMPANY>
        <PRICE>10.90</PRICE>
        <YEAR>9 mai 2019</YEAR>
        <URLPOSTER>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/f/fa/Brightburn_film_poster.png</URLPOSTER>
        <ABOUT>Brightburn is a 2019 American superhero horror film directed by David Yarovesky, written by Mark Gunn and Brian Gunn, and produced by James Gunn and Kenneth Huang. It stars Elizabeth Banks, David Denman, Jackson A. Dunn, Matt Jones and Meredith Hagner. It follows Brandon Breyer, a young boy of extraterrestrial origin reared on Earth who realizes he has superpowers. Upon learning of them and being brainwashed by the ship he arrived in, Brandon rejects his humanity and turns to evil, opting to terrorize his hometown, including his parents. The film was produced and financed by Screen Gems, Stage 6 Films, The H Collective and Troll Court Entertainment.Brightburn was announced as Untitled James Gunn Horror Project in December 2017. Aside from Gunn producing the film, his cousin Mark and brother Brian Gunn wrote the screenplay. Principal photography began in March 2018 and wrapped in May of that same year. It adapts the concept of Superman for explicit horror.Brightburn was released in the United States on May 24, 2019 by Sony Pictures Releasing. It received mixed reviews from critics, who felt that the film did not deliver on the full potential of its premise. The film earned $32 million against a budget of $6–12 million.
        </ABOUT>
        <URLVIDEO></URLVIDEO>
    </MOVIE>
</CATALOG>